And meanwhile, let us tell you that another incident has happened and that
too in Danapur, Patna.   It is being
told.  A
20-year-old boy was murdered in the Danapur area of ​​the capital.  The
body of Shivam alias Bunty was reportedly found outside the house.  Shivam has been
attacked on his head with a sharp weapon.
Shivam lived in a rented house in Danapur and he was
attacked there.  Police are investigating the matter to find out
who did this.  Let us tell you
that Shivam used to study while living with his parents
in Danapur and had
come to the village only four days ago.  The deceased's grandfather
Devendra Singh said that he had come to
sleep in his room on Sunday night.  But he
went to another room saying that
he would come after charging his mobile and then did not return.